what's happening in my life man I'm
getting older trying to figure things
out been learning a lot about myself
been learning a lot about myself I feel
like we can agree on this here this is a
nice small group meeting here I feel
like we can agree and say out loud
tonight together that we are all Afraid
of the Dark makes the noise you're
afraid of the dark let me hear you
broom full of liars listen to me listen
to me
because I see you looking around you got
a two-car garage you eat couscous now
I'm a grown person I get it listen to me
though let me be clear I don't mean if
just like these lights went out in this
room I mean all the lights in the whole
city went out I give us three minutes
before we lose our minds
the whole life your phone don't work the
whole city I give us three minutes look
around you three minutes before we lose
our minds the first minute we'll keep it
cool we'll keep it cool I go to
Applebee's once a month I know what I'm
a professional right
but around 90 95 seconds though you
start feeling stuff on the back of your
neck you ain't feel from earlier
[Laughter]
[Applause]
two minutes you start calling for people
who you thought was in the room with you
right Jessica you still in here James
mom papa hello
you start trying to listen with your
whole body every child listen with your
whole body
foreign
total chaos three minutes we start
kicking over old people where are the
kids I don't know we gotta go we out of
there three minutes
now I'm gonna tell you how I knew I was
100 afraid of the dark I'm gonna let you
know how I knew I was 100 afraid of the
dark
I was on a cruise ship a couple years
ago to let you know how my career is
going okay
I'm doing some shows and I had the ice
cream for breakfast so I wake up at 2
A.M as you do
judge means the tight budget
so I'm asleep it's a two o'clock in the
morning room is Pitch Black and I wake
up pitch black room and I just see my
bathroom door open by itself
I don't think everybody heard me
I said I'm in the middle of the ocean
I'm asleep I wake up pitch black room
and the bathroom door opens on its own I
go take the baby and I ran out the door
[Applause]
the stewardess saw me she was nervous I
was only wearing socks it was a tough
moment for both of us out here
very hot on Deck zero
so I want to be honest with you two
things number one
there was not a baby in the room that
would have been weird
[Music]
unknown baby for my safety I would do it
I would do it can we say it together
because babies are overrated thank you
listen they say you're not here you can
say it out loud here they don't know
English said out loud babies are
overrated
this is how we all can agree on this
we've all have you ever seen a baby that
looks like
he came out after his expiration date
inspire you the baby don't cover your
face you paid for this laugh so you
understand what I'm saying a baby with a
weak neck and a lazy eye you want to
push back in for 10 more minutes of
defrost a boiled chicken baby you
understand what I'm saying out here I'm
just saying every baby's not created
equal that's all I'm saying some babies
are Gerber baby some babies are Muppet
Babies you understand
what I'm saying
Davis that's all I'm saying that's all
I'm saying